{"questionWithData":[{"question":"what is Agile?","correct_ans":"iterative approach software delivery that builds software incrementally","answerData":{"a name of an angel":0.0,"kind of development plan":2.0,"treats analysis, design, coding, and testing as discrete phases the project":2.0,"iterative approach software delivery that builds software incrementally":2.0}},{"question":"What is right about Agile?","correct_ans":"All the answers are correct","answerData":{"No answer is correct":0.0,"Requirements can change and be implemented quickly":2.0,"Working software is the primary measure of success":2.0,"All the answers are correct":12.0}},{"question":"What is the main goal of a SRR?","correct_ans":"to ensure that the system requirements, products and milestones are defined","answerData":{"draft documents for the project":3.0,"has detailed development plan of the system: methods,models ,etc ":2.0,"documentation Planning and designing the user interface (GUI)":3.0,"to ensure that the system requirements, products and milestones are defined":4.0}},{"question":"What are partial requirements?","correct_ans":"incomplete requirement,that doesn\u0027t cover the required functionality in a case","answerData":{"a requirement that is partially good":1.0,"incomplete requirement,that doesn\u0027t cover the required functionality in a case":3.0,"a requirement is missing and is not described at all in the document":1.0,"a requirement that is implied in two ways":6.0}},{"question":"walkthrough peer-review is?","correct_ans":"a formal, scheduled activity where a designer presents a design to his team","answerData":{"activity where a designer presents someone else\u0027s design to the team":4.0,"a formal, scheduled activity where a designer presents a design to his team":6.0,"routine conversation with team members":0.0,"feedback conversation with the team manager":1.0}},{"question":"What is surveyed in a proposal survey?","correct_ans":"all the answers are correct","answerData":{"costs: price, resources, time":0.0,"ability to meet commitment(the organization and the customer )":0.0,"customer requirements are clarified and properly documented":1.0,"all the answers are correct":2.0}},{"question":"What is the Observer pattern?","correct_ans":"pattern that lets an object ask to be notified when another object changes","answerData":{"pattern that lets an object ask to be notified when another object changes":2.0,"pattern that creates an object and isolates a client from which class he created":3.0,"this pattern is implemented as an abstract class":1.0,"None of the answer are correct ":2.0}},{"question":"What is Client-Server architecture?","correct_ans":"collection of services that I can get from a server or a variety servers","answerData":{"more then one answer is correct":0.0,"the client always starts communicating with the server":1.0,"collection of services that I can get from a server or a variety servers":3.0,"the behavior of the system will be in the give and take method ":0.0}},{"question":"What are Lehman laws?","correct_ans":"refer to study of changes that software systems go through during their lives","answerData":{"user interface design rules":1.0,"refer to study of changes that software systems go through during their lives":2.0,"contract on system maintenance terms":2.0,"legal precedent showing how important maintenance is ":2.0}},{"question":"What is wrong to say about software maintenance costs?","correct_ans":"usually development costs are greater than maintenance costs","answerData":{"the older the software, the more it costs to develop":1,"maintenance costs are usually higher than development costs":1,"usually development costs are greater than maintenance costs":4,"Maintenance costs more than hardware ":5}},{"question":"What is driver?","correct_ans":"component that replaces the UNIT environment and activates test component ","answerData":{"the component on which we want to perform the test":2.0,"a component that transmits test results":0.0,"component that replaces the UNIT environment and activates test component ":4.0,"a component that makes a simple simulation of the world around it":0.0}},{"question":"What is the difference between a \u0027white box\u0027 and a \u0027black box\u0027 test?","correct_ans":"black box refer component in the system but not his code compared to white","answerData":{"black box refer component in the system but not his code compared to white":2.0,"white box refer component in the system but not his code compared to black ":0.0,"there is no difference":2.0,"various staff members perform the tests":0.0}},{"question":"What is SDP?","correct_ans":"has detailed development plan of the system: methods,models ,etc ","answerData":{"none of the above":0.0,"has detailed development plan of the system: methods,models ,etc ":0.0,"documentation Planning and designing the user interface (GUI)":2.0,"to ensure that the system requirements, products and milestones are defined":1.0}},{"question":"What on the list is a type of survey?","correct_ans":"all of the answers are correct","answerData":{"all of the answers are correct":3.0,"product release review ":2.0,"per reviews":3.0,"product approval":1.0}}]}